[{"answer": " Hey, Joseph. This history course I am taking is kind of hard. I have a group repor", "docId": "07-03", "aSentId": 12, "question": "", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": " What is it about", "docId": "07-03", "aSentId": 16, "question": " Hey, Joseph. This history course I am taking is kind of hard. I have a group repor", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " Its going to be a mock trial and I have to describe the process of jury selection", "docId": "07-03", "aSentId": 17, "question": " What is it about", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " Oh.  I know a little about that", "docId": "07-03", "aSentId": 18, "question": " Its going to be a mock trial and I have to describe the process of jury selection", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " Really?  Can you help me with some of the information", "docId": "07-03", "aSentId": 19, "question": " Oh.  I know a little about that", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " Sure", "docId": "07-03", "aSentId": 20, "question": " Really?  Can you help me with some of the information", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " Ok.  People who live in the city where the trial is taking place are selected for th", "docId": "07-03", "aSentId": 21, "question": " Sure", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " Yes, I think the courts have a list of people who have drivers licenses and the", "docId": "07-03", "aSentId": 27, "question": " Ok.  People who live in the city where the trial is taking place are selected for th", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " Wow.  So anyone who has a drivers license could be chosen for the jury", "docId": "07-03", "aSentId": 29, "question": " Yes, I think the courts have a list of people who have drivers licenses and the", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": " Yep. I think the court has a computer that randomly selects from that list. The", "docId": "07-03", "aSentId": 33, "question": " Wow.  So anyone who has a drivers license could be chosen for the jury", "qSentId": 32},{"answer": " Oh, ok", "docId": "07-03", "aSentId": 37, "question": " Yep. I think the court has a computer that randomly selects from that list. The", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": "Its a law that if you get a letter in the mail, that you must appear at th", "docId": "07-03", "aSentId": 38, "question": " Oh, ok", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " What if you cant go", "docId": "07-03", "aSentId": 42, "question": "Its a law that if you get a letter in the mail, that you must appear at th", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " The only time you dont have to go is if you already have airline tickets booked", "docId": "07-03", "aSentId": 43, "question": " What if you cant go", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " But if you cant go in for jury duty, how do you prove that to the court", "docId": "07-03", "aSentId": 47, "question": " The only time you dont have to go is if you already have airline tickets booked", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": "You have to show proof of the airline tickets that you purchased or a note fro", "docId": "07-03", "aSentId": 48, "question": " But if you cant go in for jury duty, how do you prove that to the court", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " What happens when the people arrive at the courthouse", "docId": "07-03", "aSentId": 52, "question": "You have to show proof of the airline tickets that you purchased or a note fro", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " I know when they get to the courthouse, theyre instructed to answer question", "docId": "07-03", "aSentId": 53, "question": " What happens when the people arrive at the courthouse", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " What kind of questions do they ask them", "docId": "07-03", "aSentId": 58, "question": " I know when they get to the courthouse, theyre instructed to answer question", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " Mostly they ask them questions about the case, to make sure they dont kno", "docId": "07-03", "aSentId": 59, "question": " What kind of questions do they ask them", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " I know that the jury is usually made up of men and women, who represen", "docId": "07-03", "aSentId": 65, "question": " Mostly they ask them questions about the case, to make sure they dont kno", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " Right", "docId": "07-03", "aSentId": 69, "question": " I know that the jury is usually made up of men and women, who represen", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": " If someones selected for a jury, then what happens", "docId": "07-03", "aSentId": 70, "question": " Right", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": "Then they must appear in court every day of the trail to listen to witnesses o", "docId": "07-03", "aSentId": 71, "question": " If someones selected for a jury, then what happens", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " Ok.  That information will be really helpful for our group report.  I think I ca", "docId": "07-03", "aSentId": 75, "question": "Then they must appear in court every day of the trail to listen to witnesses o", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " No.  Actually, I got selected for jury duty last month for the first time.  I got th", "docId": "07-03", "aSentId": 82, "question": " Ok.  That information will be really helpful for our group report.  I think I ca", "qSentId": 81},{"answer": " Were you selected", "docId": "07-03", "aSentId": 86, "question": " No.  Actually, I got selected for jury duty last month for the first time.  I got th", "qSentId": 85},{"answer": " Yep, I was.  I was on the jury of a trial that lasted for 14 days", "docId": "07-03", "aSentId": 87, "question": " Were you selected", "qSentId": 86},{"answer": " Thats a long time.  Were you mad that you had to be on the jury for so long", "docId": "07-03", "aSentId": 88, "question": " Yep, I was.  I was on the jury of a trial that lasted for 14 days", "qSentId": 87},{"answer": " Nah.  I was happy to do it.  Plus, I got out of work and class for two weeks", "docId": "07-03", "aSentId": 89, "question": " Thats a long time.  Were you mad that you had to be on the jury for so long", "qSentId": 88},{"answer": " I see.  Well, thank you for helping me get started on this report", "docId": "07-03", "aSentId": 90, "question": " Nah.  I was happy to do it.  Plus, I got out of work and class for two weeks", "qSentId": 89},{"answer": " No problem.  Good luck on it", "docId": "07-03", "aSentId": 91, "question": " I see.  Well, thank you for helping me get started on this report", "qSentId": 90}]
